[
	{
		"question": "A fresh start, trust, significant step into unknown",
		"answer": "↑ The Fool"
	},
	{
		"question": "Inner wisdom, intuition, mystery, expert or expert advise",
		"answer": "↑ The Magician"
	},
	{
		"question": "Nurturing, creation, abundance, hidden knowledge, something not yet seen",
		"answer": "↑ The High Priestess"
	},
	{
		"question": "You are queen, creating something, birth to new idea",
		"answer": "↑ The Empress"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ambition, control, direction, leadership",
		"answer": "↑ The Emperor"
	},
	{
		"question": "Belief, guidance, higher purpose, self development, seeking mentorship",
		"answer": "↑ The Hierophant"
	},
	{
		"question": "Partnerships, choices, balance, obsession & passion",
		"answer": "↑ The Lovers"
	},
	{
		"question": "Willpower, focus, determination, advancement",
		"answer": "↑ The Chariot"
	},
	{
		"question": "Strength, courage, inner power, confidence",
		"answer": "↑ Strength"
	},
	{
		"question": "Contemplation, retreat, introspection",
		"answer": "↑ The Hermit"
	},
	{
		"question": "Turning point, change, fate, evolutionary change",
		"answer": "↑ Wheel of Fortune"
	},
	{
		"question": "Justice, truth, accountability, legal matters, true path, what is right for you",
		"answer": "↑ Justice"
	},
	{
		"question": "Sacrifice, release, letting go",
		"answer": "↑ The Hanged Man"
	},
	{
		"question": "Endings, transformation, rebirth, something ends - something begins",
		"answer": "↑ Death"
	},
	{
		"question": "Moderation, balance, healing, patience",
		"answer": "↑ Temperance"
	},
	{
		"question": "Challenge, upheaval, revelation, temptetion, prisonner of your own temptations",
		"answer": "↑ The Devil"
	},
	{
		"question": "Chaos, Crisis, revelation, awakening, rebuild your life",
		"answer": "↑ The Tower"
	},
	{
		"question": "Hope, renewal, serenity, inspiration, guidance",
		"answer": "↑ The Star"
	},
	{
		"question": "Illusion, fear, subconscious, hidden soon to be revealed",
		"answer": "↑ The Moon"
	},
	{
		"question": "Clarity, enlightenment, truth, success, hapinnes",
		"answer": "↑ The Sun"
	},
	{
		"question": "Judgment, rebirth, reckoning, you are awoken to make the most of your life, complte chage of direction",
		"answer": "↑ Judgement"
	},
	{
		"question": "Completion, arrival, fulfillment, world is at your feet",
		"answer": "↑ The World"
	},
	{
		"question": "New emotional relationship, New beginnings in emotions, inspiration",
		"answer": "↓ Ace of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional partnership and mutual understanding in love, business",
		"answer": "↓ Two of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Celebration, creativity, friendship, gathering",
		"answer": "↓ Three of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional disinterest, re-evaluation of feelings",
		"answer": "↓ Four of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional loss, grieviing, Choices in emotions, desire for more",
		"answer": "↓ Five of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional nostalgia, Recovery, appreciation, connection",
		"answer": "↓ Six of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotionally confusing, illusionary, a lot, Transition, letting go, moving forward",
		"answer": "↓ Seven of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional ability to get over past emotions looking forward to new ones",
		"answer": "↓ Eight of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional fullfillment, balance, Reflection, meditation",
		"answer": "↓ Nine of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional Happy ever after, celebration, wishes granted",
		"answer": "↓ Ten of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "New emotional beginnings, invitations",
		"answer": "↓ Page of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional movement forward, romantic openness, idealism",
		"answer": "↓ Knight of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional intelligence, graciousness, mother, sister, friend",
		"answer": "↓ Queen of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "Emotional Compassion, connection, responsibility, leadership",
		"answer": "↓ King of Cups"
	},
	{
		"question": "New financial beginning, Spark of creative energy, ambition in work",
		"answer": "↓ Ace of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Initial financial decisions or partnerships",
		"answer": "↓ Two of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Collaboration, skill-building, apprenticeships",
		"answer": "↓ Three of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Stability, planning, practicality",
		"answer": "↓ Four of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Loss, change, reassessment of resources, financial milestone",
		"answer": "↓ Five of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Recovery, generosity, sharing resources",
		"answer": "↓ Six of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Hard work, growth, perseverance",
		"answer": "↓ Seven of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Practical completion, long-term success, skilled well established, busy",
		"answer": "↓ Eight of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Financial fullfillment, Abundance, material satisfaction, luxury",
		"answer": "↓ Nine of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Wealth, legacy, family prosperity",
		"answer": "↓ Ten of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "New financial path,New opportunity in commerce or learning",
		"answer": "↓ Page of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Advancemnt in financial, Ambitious action in career and finances",
		"answer": "↓ Knight of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Nurturing responsibility, Practical wisdom",
		"answer": "↓ Queen of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "Sound financial leadership, stability",
		"answer": "↓ King of Pentacles"
	},
	{
		"question": "New creative spark, willpower in action",
		"answer": "↓ Ace of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Choices in creativity, directionless energy",
		"answer": "↓ Two of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creating something and put it out in the world and wait for return",
		"answer": "↓ Three of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative Stability or stalled energy",
		"answer": "↓ Four of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative challenge, Conflict, tension, same level (colleagues)",
		"answer": "↓ Five of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative Victory, recognition, competition",
		"answer": "↓ Six of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative Abundance of ideas, multiple options",
		"answer": "↓ Seven of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative Skill development, perseverance in craft, Busy",
		"answer": "↓ Eight of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Rush of energy, swift progress, maybe a bit tired from it",
		"answer": "↓ Nine of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative completion and mastery of endeavors",
		"answer": "↓ Ten of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative new path, message, proposals, opportunities",
		"answer": "↓ Page of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative advancement, Action, adventure, charismatic energy",
		"answer": "↓ Knight of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative Inspiration, leadership, warmth",
		"answer": "↓ Queen of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "Creative drive, charisma, vision, leadrship",
		"answer": "↓ King of Wands"
	},
	{
		"question": "New intellectual idea, clarity of thought",
		"answer": "↓ Ace of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Decision-making, intelectual planning",
		"answer": "↓ Two of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Heartbroken, intellectual loss, communication",
		"answer": "↓ Three of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Resilience after heartbreak, recovery, take a break",
		"answer": "↓ Four of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Conflict, stress, tension in mind, people can help you, seek help",
		"answer": "↓ Five of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Disillusionment, reevaluation of beliefs, smother waters",
		"answer": "↓ Six of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Deception, lookout",
		"answer": "↓ Seven of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Traped in their thoughts",
		"answer": "↓ Eight of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Thoughts are bugging you too much, Reflection",
		"answer": "↓ Nine of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Completion of mental projects, resolution, as worst as it gets, only improve from here",
		"answer": "↓ Ten of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "New intellectual path, new insight",
		"answer": "↓ Page of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Intelectual advancement, Curiosity, vigilance, exploration",
		"answer": "↓ Knight of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Intellectual clarity, unbiased judgment",
		"answer": "↓ Queen of Swords"
	},
	{
		"question": "Intellectual Authority, strategic thinking",
		"answer": "↓ King of Swords"
	}
]
